http://www.electrobattery.com/privacy.php

Chargers
- Odyssey (PDF)
- Associated Equipment (PDF)
SLA (UPS/TELCOM/Power Protection Applications)
Warranty
- Odyssey (PDF)
Battery Chargers
SLA Batteries (UPS/TELCOM/Power Protection Applications)
Motive Power/Golf Cart/RV Batteries
Renewable Energy/Solar/Photovoltaic Batteries
Engine Starting/Energy Storage
Privacy & Security
Electro Battery Co. Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:
Electro Battery Co. Inc.
Information Automatically Logged:
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.
Personal Information:
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
External Links:
This site contains links to other sites. Electro Battery Co. Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security:
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Contacting the Web Site: If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: info@electrobattery.com
Home
| Privacy/Security
| About Us | Contact
Us
230 West Parkway US · Pompton Plains, NJ 07444 Phone: 973-835-3334. Fax: 973-835-2332
Batteries (UPS/TELCOM/Power Protection Applications) | Motive
